//Added harry Potter questions to the array 
let questions = [
    {
      question: "What is the name of Harry Potter's owl?",
      optionA: "Hedwig",
      optionB: "Pigwidgeon",
      optionC: "Hermes",
      optionD: "Errol",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q1
    },
    
    {
      question: "What was the name of Lord Voldemort's loyal snake?",
      optionA: "Buckbeak",
      optionB: "Aragog",
      optionC: "Nagini",
      optionD: "Fluffy",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q2
    },
  
    {
      question: "Name the killing curse",
      optionA: "Crucio",
      optionB: "Avada Kedavra",
      optionC: "Sectumsempra",
      optionD: "Imperio",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q3
    },
  
    {
  
      question: "What is the five digit code that one needs to dial to get inside the Ministry of Magic?",
      optionA: "6-4-4-2-6",
      optionB: "6-3-3-4-2",
      optionC: "6-2-5-5-2",
      optionD: "6-2-4-4-2",
      correctOption: "optionD" //Q4
    },
  
    {
      question: "What was Harry’s Patronus?",
      optionA: "Stag",
      optionB: "Jack Russell Terrier",
      optionC: "Otter",
      optionD: "Phoenix",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q5
  
  
    },
  
    {
      question: "What's inside Harry Potter's wand?",
      optionA: "Dragon Heartstring",
      optionB: "Unknown",
      optionC: "Phoenix feather",
      optionD: "Unicorn hair",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q6
    },
  
    {
      question: "In the Ministry of Magic, for which department does Arthur Weasley work?",
      optionA: "Ministry of Magic Witch Watchers",
      optionB: "Misuse of Muggle artifacts",
      optionC: "Improper Use of Magic Office",
      optionD: "Muggle Liaison Office",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q7
    },
  
    {
      question: "Who among the Marauders was also known as Prongs?",
      optionA: "James Potter",
      optionB: "Sirius Black",
      optionC: "Remus Lupin",
      optionD: "Peter Pettigrew",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q8
    },
  
    {
      question: "What is the name of Nymphadora Tonk's Aunt?",
      optionA: "Laurena Lestrange",
      optionB: "Balbine Lestrange",
      optionC: "Bellatrix Lestrange",
      optionD: "Leta Lestrange",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q9
    },
  
    {
      question: "What is Harry's vault number in Gringotts?",
      optionA: "657",
      optionB: "687",
      optionC: "697",
      optionD: "667",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q10
    },
  
    {
      question: "How is a Basilisk born?",
      optionA: "A cock egg born below the dark",
      optionB: "A cock egg born below a rock",
      optionC: "A cock egg born below a tree",
      optionD: "A cock egg born below a toad",
      correctOption: "optionD"  //Q11
    },
  
    {
      question: "What chess piece does Luna's house resemble during the Golden Trio's visit?",
      optionA: "A knight",
      optionB: "A bishop",
      optionC: "A pawn",
      optionD: "A rook",
      correctOption: "optionD"  //Q12
  
    },
  
    {
      question: "In Knockturn Alley, Harry watches as Draco examines a cursed necklace that has killed how many muggle owners?",
      optionA: "15",
      optionB: "22",
      optionC: "19",
      optionD: "12",
      correctOption: "optionC"  //Q13
    },
  
    {
      question: "What organization did Hermione start in her 4th year?",
      optionA: "Wizzards against the Dark Arts",
      optionB: "Society for the promotion of Elfish Welfare",
      optionC: "Witches for Equal Rights",
      optionD: "Dumbledore's Army",
      correctOption: "optionB"  //Q14
  
    },
  
    {
      question: "What potion did Harry take in order to get Slughorn's memories?",
      optionA: "Felix Felicis",
      optionB: "Polyjucie Potion",
      optionC: "Essence of Dittany",
      optionD: "Alihotsy Draught",
      correctOption: "optionA"  //Q15
  
    },
  
    {
      question: "What did Dumbledore leave for Hermione in his will?",
      optionA: "Cloak of invisibility",
      optionB: "An enchanted purse",
      optionC: "The Tales of Beadle the Bard",
      optionD: "A bezoar",
      correctOption: "optionC"  //Q16
  
    },
  
    {
      question: "What relation was Sirius Black to Harry?",
      optionA: "Cousin",
      optionB: "Godfather",
      optionC: "Uncle",
      optionD: "Family friend",
      correctOption: "optionB"  //Q17
    },
  
    {
      question: "Who is the owner of a sorting hat",
      optionA: "Rowena Ravenclaw",
      optionB: "Godric Gryffindor",
      optionC: "Salazar Slytherin",
      optionD: "Helga Hufflepuff",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q18
    },
  
    {
      question: "Name the mother of Severus Snape, who was a pure-blooded witch",
      optionA: "Emma",
      optionB: "Emily",
      optionC: "Elieen",
      optionD: "Everly",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q19
    },
  
    {
      question: "Name the warden of the orphanage from where Voldemort came from?",
      optionA: "Mr. Cole",
      optionB: "Mrs. Cole",
      optionC: "Mr Smith",
      optionD: "Mrs Smith",
      correctOption: "optionB"  //Q20
    },
  
    {
      question: "Which school Harry planned to go before he decided to go to Hogwarts?",
      optionA: "Johnson City High",
      optionB: "Jamestown High",
      optionC: "Stonewall High",
      optionD: "Ridgeback High",
      correctOption: "optionC"  //Q21
    },
  
    {
      question: "What plants are the Gryffindors and the Hufflepuffs working with on their first day of second-year Herbology?",
      optionA: "Mandrakes",
      optionB: "Gillyweed",
      optionC: "Bubotuber",
      optionD: "Devil's Snare",
      correctOption: "optionA"  //Q22
  
    },
  
    {
      question: "Who is the Death Eater who became the Headmaster of Durmstrang School after Voldemort lost his power?",
      optionA: "Fenrir Greyback",
      optionB: "Lucius Malfoy",
      optionC: "Severus Snape",
      optionD: "Igor Karkaroff",
      correctOption: "optionD" //Q23
    },
  
    {
      question: "In the Hall of Prophecy, which row holds Harry and Voldemort's prophecy?",
      optionA: "57",
      optionB: "97",
      optionC: "87",
      optionD: "67",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q24
    },
  
    {
      question: "Which dragon does Cedric Diggory get for his first task during the Triwizard Tournament?",
      optionA: "Welsh Green",
      optionB: "Chinese Fireball",
      optionC: "Swedish Short-Snout",
      optionD: "Hungarian Horntail",
      correctOption: "optionB"  //Q25
  
    }
  
    {
      question: "In the game of Quidditch, how many possible fouls are there?",
      optionA: "500",
      optionB: "1000",
      optionC: "700",
      optionD: "800",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q26
    },
  
    {
      question: "What creature is Aragog?",
      optionA: "Ashwinder",
      optionB: "Basilisk",
      optionC: "Acromantula",
      optionD: "Billywig",
      correctOption: "optionC"  //Q27
    },
  
    {
      question: "What spell would you use to open a door?",
      optionA: "Alohomora",
      optionB: "Lumos",
      optionC: "Riddikulus",
      optionD: "Avada Kedavra",
      correctOption: "optionA" //28
    },
  
    {
      question: "How did Neville Longbottom help defeat the dark lord?",
      optionA: "Killing the snake",
      optionB: "Staring at the snake",
      optionC: "Kicking the snake",
      optionD: "Burning the snake",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q29
    },
  
    {
      question: "After visiting Gringotts, which shop does Harry first go to in Diagon Alley?",
      optionA: "Flourish and Blotts",
      optionB: "Madam Malkin's Robes For All Occasions",
      optionC: "Slugs and Jigger's Apothecary",
      optionD: "Twilfitt and Tatting’s",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q30
    },
  
    {
      question: "For how many years did the Weasleys have Scabbers as a pet?",
      optionA: "11",
      optionB: "8",
      optionC: "10",
      optionD: "12",
      correctOption: "optionD" //Q31
  
    },
  
    {
      question: "What did Harry receive from the Dursley’s on his first Christmas at Hogwarts?",
      optionA: "A ten-pence piece",
      optionB: "A twenty-pence piece",
      optionC: "A fifty-pence piece",
      optionD: "Nothing!",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q32
    },
  
    {
      question: "4.	What was Hagrid's pet dog called?",
      optionA: "Fang",
      optionB: "Fluffy",
      optionC: "Norbert",
      optionD: "Mosag",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q33
    },
  
    {
      question: "What is the maximum speed that a firebolt broomstick can reach?",
      optionA: "120 mph",
      optionB: "150 mph",
      optionC: "200 mph",
      optionD: "300 mph",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q34
    },
  
    {
      question: "Where did Hermione first apparate to after Harry, Ron and Hermione flee from Bill and Fleurs’s wedding from Voldemort?",
      optionA: "Oxford Circus",
      optionB: "Tottenham court road",
      optionC: "Picadily Circus",
      optionD: "Trafalgar Square",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q35
    },
    
    {
      question: "What was the name of the Irish chaser that scored the first goal in the Quidditch World Cup?",
      optionA: "Mullet",
      optionB: "Troy",
      optionC: "Moran",
      optionD: "Conolly",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q36
    },
  
    {
      question: "How many Horcruxes were made?",
      optionA: "10",
      optionB: "7",
      optionC: "8",
      optionD: "6",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q37
    },
  
    {
      question: "Hannah Abbott is sorted into which house?",
      optionA: "Slytherin",
      optionB: "Ravenclaw",
      optionC: "Gryffindor",
      optionD: "Hufflepuff",
      correctOption: "optionD" //Q38
    },
  
    {
      question: "What is the location of Azkaban?",
      optionA: "Mediterranean Sea",
      optionB: "Baltic sea",
      optionC: "The Red sea",
      optionD: "The North sea",
      correctOption: "optionD" //Q39
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Who said, "The wand chooses the wizard, Mr. Potter."',
      optionA: "Ollivander",
      optionB: "Dumbledore",
      optionC: "Hagrid",
      optionD: "Hermione",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q40
    },
  
    {
      question: "What spell would you use to conjure a patronus?",
      optionA: "Lumos",
      optionB: "Expecto Patronum",
      optionC: "Aguamenti",
      optionD: "Expelliarmus",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q41
    },
  
    {
      question: "How did Cedric Diggory die?",
      optionA: "He was killed by Peter Pettigrew with the Killing Curse",
      optionB: "He was killed by Bellatrix Lestrange with the killing curse",
      optionC: "Harry Potter killed him, by accident",
      optionD: "He was killed by lord Voldemort",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q42
    },
  
    {
      question: "Which platform at Kings Cross Station do Hogwarts' pupils use to access the Hogwarts Express?",
      optionA: "8 3/4",
      optionB: "1 3/4",
      optionC: "3 3/4",
      optionD: "9 3/4",
      correctOption: "optionD" //Q43
    },
  
    {
      question: "When was the first Harry Potter book released?",
      optionA: "1992",
      optionB: "1995",
      optionC: "1997",
      optionD: "1999",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q44
    },
  
    {
      question: "When was the first Harry Potter film released?",
      optionA: "2000",
      optionB: "2001",
      optionC: "2003",
      optionD: "1999",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q45
    },
  
    {
      question: "How many copies of Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone were printed in the book's first print run?",
      optionA: "100",
      optionB: "250",
      optionC: "500",
      optionD: "300",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q46
    },
  
    {
      question: "Who was the first person seen at the beginning of the movie, 'Harry Potter and The Sorcerer's Stone'?",
      optionA: "Bartemius Crouch Jnr",
      optionB: "Professor Snape",
      optionC: "Professor Mcgonagall",
      optionD: "Professor Dumbledore",
      correctOption: "optionD" //Q47
    },
  
    {
      question: "After escaping from the Chamber of Secrets with Fawkes, where do Ron, Harry, Ginny, and Professor Lockhart go?",
      optionA: "Professor's McGonagall's Office",
      optionB: "Professor Snape Office",
      optionC: "Professor Dumbledore Office",
      optionD: "Professor Fortinbras Office",
      correctOption: "optionA" //Q48
    },
  
    {
      question: "Which professional Quidditch team does Cho Chang support?",
      optionA: "Montrose Magpies",
      optionB: "Wigtown Wanderers",
      optionC: "Tutshill Tornados",
      optionD: "Ballycastle Bats",
      correctOption: "optionC" //Q49
    },
  
    {
      question: "Who is the heir of Slytherin as revealed in 'Harry Potter And The Chamber Of Secrets'?",
      optionA: "Rosier",
      optionB: "Tom Riddle",
      optionC: "Lestrange",
      optionD: "Avery I",
      correctOption: "optionB" //Q50
    },
  
  ];